Sorry.
The fetus was lost.
Mr. Wang Jiming
died on the spot.
It turns out that a person can really lose everything
in one night.
And being at the end of one's rope
is not just something that happens in the movies.
Sorry, ma'am.
The case is closed.
This is dereliction of duty.
The official hasty closure
made me realize that this was not a simple accident.
Anger,
helplessness,
danger,
fear,
they were like gnats clinging to my bones, following me everywhere.
But in the fire,
I was reduced to ashes,
and even my identity was gone.
[I can only wander around]
[in this real]
[yet virtual world like a ghost,]
[crawling painfully,]
[and struggling to survive.]
Mr. Lin,
Guan Yu is here.
Okay.
Then, Mr. Lin,
please prepare the contract.
Welcome Guan Law Firm
to join Lin Group.
My pleasure.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
Here's the contract.
First,
Zhao Zhiwei's case must be resolved as soon as possible.
Second,
help me find trouble with Liu Yaping.
Third,
the legal team of Lin Group
is not good enough.
I need a sharp and straight
blade to help me
rebuild the rules.
It's challenging.
I like it.
Pleasure to work with you, Mr. Lin.
Yes.
I'll send it over right away.
Ms. Liu,
welcome.
Where's Jiming?
Is he busy?
I'm sorry, Ms. Liu.
Mr. Lin
is in a meeting with Lawyer Guan.
Lawyer Guan?
The new general counsel,
Guan Tiantian.
Lawyer Guan.
The Prince.
I didn't expect
Mr. Lin to be into political maneuvering.
When you decide to do something,
do it to the extreme.
I think
Guan Lu knows how to be extreme.
How to control foxes
and lions.
My favorite chapter.
Oh.
Then
which one am I?
You
are a
little lion
who wants to be a king.
Jiming.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Lin.
Miss Liu
insisted on coming in.
I couldn't stop her.
You go out first.
Yes.
Jiming,
am I coming at a bad time?
Sorry to interrupt
your work discussion.
What's the matter?
I'm working in the audit department.
My brother and Auntie Wen think
my joining the Lin Group
will be very helpful
to the company's future plans.
From now on,
we are colleagues.
How come I didn't know about this?
That's why I'm here to tell you.
Besides,
Guan Lu was promoted to the general counsel,
and I joined the audit department,
isn't that reasonable?
Guan Lu, what do you think?
Welcome, Ms. Liu.
The audit department is a key part of the company.
With Ms. Liu on board,
I'm sure
it will help us run more smoothly.
Yeah,
Especially to standardize
some employees who rose to power
through unconventional means.
Jiming,
my brother asked me to remind you
that our family
has invested a lot of resources
in the project in the south of the city.
He hopes you
can distinguish right from wrong
Don't be influenced by outsiders
and make wrong decisions.
You don't need to
interfere in the company's decisions.
I won't.
I just want to remind you that
Auntie Wen and my brother
are watching.
Guannv Law Firm.
The Lin Group is very tricky.
Be careful.
Don't trip over someone else's shoes
and hurt yourself.
Thank you for the reminder, Ms. Liu.
But
I'm used to looking at data and rules first.
I won't know
until I walk through it.
And
currently, there aren't many people
who can help Mr. Lin
seem
to be insufficient.
You...
Liu Yaru,
Guann Law Firm is a professional firm.
Her work is directly responsible to me.
Watch your words.
Jiming,
I...
Mr. Lin,
Ms. Liu is just concerned.
Since Ms. Liu has joined the audit department,
we can
send her a copy
of the non-core summary reports
in the project risk book.
After all,
more perspectives
are always better.
Sure,
just arrange it.
Okay.
Good.
Guan Tiantian,
we have plenty of time.
Actually,
you don't have to
report to her.
A non-core bulletin
makes her feel included.
It's much cheaper
than making her feel excluded
than having her feel excluded
and causing trouble everywhere.
After all,
you have to consider
her brother.
You know the Lin Group very well.
I believe
you are the best choice
to be my knife.
I hope I can be more than your tool.
Ms Lin.
Brother,
please find someone
to investigate her background thoroughly.
I don't care how much it costs.
I want to know if this Guan Tiantian
is really who she claims to be.
Sigh.
Is it worth it
for Lin Jiming?
It's up to me to decide.
Besides,
she has started to target our Liu family.
Brother.
Okay.
I'll help you investigate.
But to be honest,
Lin Jiming
is too outrageous now.
Can you say less?
Not targeting him
is the best help you can give me.
You know nothing.
Bah.
Yu,
you must have the wrong person.
I'm sorry.
This is a members-only club.
I know that.
Then I want to become a member.
Let me in.
I'm sorry.
Non-members are not allowed in.
Then how do I become a member?
Should I meet your manager?
Then call him out for me.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
[She divorced and took away 300 million yuan.]
[What makes]
[Wang Shuer, who drives the King crazy]
[and even tried to kill himself, so charming?]
[It is said that]
[Wang Shuer had studied]
[at a mysterious training institution.]
[The institution is dedicated to creating socialites.]
Socialites?
S club.
Xiaoyu,
is that you?
Xiaoyu.
Xiaoyu died long ago.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Oh.
This is
a gift for your new job.
Thank you, Mr. Lin.
Ah.
Don't call me Mr. Lin after work.
Ah?
What's wrong?
You don't seem very happy.
Did something happen?
I have some things I must do,
but they're really hard to achieve.
Sometimes I just feel
so tired,
so lonely.
If you're willing,
I can help you.
Even if it's just to use me?